Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
James Britton papers
- Diaries, 1918-1935, Series 4:; (Box 1-2; 1.5 linear feet)
  - Diaries, 1918-1935, Subseries 4.1:
    Groll, Albert: XXXVII, 47, 100; XXXI, 61-2, 79; XXXIII, 8, 15; XXXIV, 1-2; XXXV, 20; XXXVI, 11-13; XXXV B, 4; XXXVI, 23
    Gruppe, Charles P: XXXVIII, 40, 43
    Hackett, Francis: XXVI, 132
    Hafner, Charles Andrew: XXXI, 38, 80; XXXIV, 1, 14; XXXV, 1, 44, 55, 57, 60 63, 67, 77, 90-2, 120, 129, 130, 133; XXXV B, 1, 5; XXXVI, 14, 20, 25, 73
    Hafner, Victor: XXXV, 55, 66, 92, 94
    Hale, Philip L.: XXV, 40, 52; XXVII, 48, 56, 117; XXXV, 16l; XXXVI, 80
    Hall, Frederick: XXVI, 127
    Halpert, Samuel: XXVI, 135; XXVII, 26l XXIX, 6, 39, 80
    Hambridge, Jay: XXXV B, 1-5
    Hamilton, McClure: XXXIII, 25
    Hardie, Robert Gordon: XXXVIII, 51
    Harris, Frank: XXVII, 110
    Harris, Sam: XXXVIII, 45
    Hart, Charles Henry: XXXI, 1
    Hartman, Bertram: XXVII, 25l; XXIX, 55
    Hassam, Childe: XXV, 97; XXVII, 34, 48; XXIX, 55; XXX, 28l XXXI, 1, 73; XXXII, 1; XXXIII, 14, 20, 34; XXXV, 25, 80-2, 119; XXXVI, 10; XXXVIII, 91
    Haverty, J. J.: XXXVII, 17-21; XXXVIII, 17
    Hawthorne, Charles W: XXX, 55-6
    Haydn, Josef: XXV; XXVI, 97; XXVII, 79-80, 113; XXXIV, 17-20; XXXV, 46, 127; XXXVI, 15-6, 28-9, 33; XXXVIII, 74, 81-2, 94-5
    Haytner, George: XXIII, 43
    Healey, George P. A.: XXXI, 21-2; XXXVIII, 50
    Hecht, Victor
    Heney, Charles: XXVII, 83l XXVI, 51, 53, 89
    Henri, Robert: XXVI, 46, 98; XXVII, 53-4, 115-7; XXXI, 20; XXXII, 46; XXXIII, 25; XXXV, 107
    Herbert, Victor: XXXVI, 15
    Higgins, Eugene: XXVI, 45-6, 60, 84, 136-7; XXVII, 25, 53, 73, 75-6, 95-8; XXIX, 3-5, 12; XXXI, 66-8, 72-4; XXXIII, 8, 23; XXXV, 6, 9, 20, 23, 108-9; XXXVI, 22-3; XXXVII, 14-5
    Hines, William Clocker: XXXVII
    Hooker, J.: XXVI, 31-3; XXXVIII, 105, 107
    Hopkinson, Charles: XXV, 40
    Hoppin, Charles A.: XXXI, 90; XXXII, 32-3; XXXIII, 19, 33, 38; XXXIV, 14, 23-4; XXXV, 6, 11-2, 24, 39, 55, 76, 88, 90; XXXV B, 12
    Horne, Grace: XXV, 53, 69, 81
    Horton, Herbert: XXXVI, 20
    Howell, Felicia Waldo: XXV; XXVI, 29
    Huneker, James: XXXI, 18; XXXVI, 10; XXXVIII, 78
    Hunt, William Morris: XXX, 45; XXXIII, 35, 37
    Huntington, Dan: XXX, 13, 16; XXXVIII, 51
    Ingres: XXX, 23; XXIV
    Inman, Henry: XXX, 17; XXXV, 87
    Innes, George: XXXI, 66
    Inukai, Kyohei: XXXV, 110-111, 132, 136; XXXVI, 7, 25, 28-9, 36, 38, 40, 42-3, 46, 50-6, 64; XXXV B, 10, 13, 26-7; XXXVII, 16, 39, 42; XXXVIII, 4, 8-9, 18, 20, 34-5, 40-1l 82, 85, 88, 90-100
    Jaccaci, August: XXVII, 35
    Jacobs, Michel: XXXV, 133
    Johnson, Eastman: XXXIII, 19
    Jones, Paul: XXXV, 137; XXXV B, 21
    Judson, Alice: XXVI, 104; XXVII, 5-6, 38-9, 41, 60, 64, 96-7; XXIX, 3, 36; XXXIV, 13; XXXV, 73; XXXVI, 14, 30, 54, 69-70; XXXVIII, 9-90
    Katzief, J. D.: XXXVII, 35-7; XXXVIII, 41
    Keefe, Lucia: XXVV, 52
    Keller, Deane: XXVII; XXXVIII, 94, 103; XXXIX, 3
    Kennedy, E. D.: XXIX, 63
    Kenny, M.: XXV, 86
    Kensett, John F.: XXVII, 52-3
    Kent, Rockwell: XXIX, 33, 43
    Kevorkian: XXIX, 10, 45, 55; XXXIII, 19
    Kidder, Frank: XXVI, 133
    Kimbel, Richard: XXV, 91-2, 105; XXVI, 104, 113; XXVII, 52, 69; XXXI, 80; XXXIII, 9; XXXV, 123-4, 131, 168; XXXVIII, 85
    Kingore, C. Grant: XXVII, 32, 76, 117; XXIX, 43
    Kinnis: XXXVII, 44
    Kitson, Henry Hudson: XXV, 65; XXXVI, 66-7
    Klauser, Ella: XXVI, 113
    Kneisel, Franz: XXXVI, 15
    Knoedlers: XXVI, 136, 180-1; XXVII, 115; XXIX, 47, 58
    Kone, Irma: XXVI, 29
    Konody, Paul G.: XXIX, 63
    Kraushaar, John: XXVI, 42; XXXVIII
    Kress: XXV, 29, 107; XXVI, 42-3; XXVII, 118; XXIX, 1, 21, 54; XXXV, 14, 16
    Kronberg, Louis: XXV, 37, 53, 64, 83, 95-7; XXXI, 3-4, 83; XXXV, 16; XXXVII, 23
    Kuehne, Max: XXVI, 42
    Kusnitzky, Abraham: XXXI, 47; XXXVI, 83
    La Farge, John: XXXVIII, 64
    Langzettel, George: XXIX, 44
    Lanier, Henry: XXVII, 116
    Lathrop, W. L.: XXXV, 81-2
    Laurens, Jean Paul: XXXIII, 21
    Lawlor, Frederick: XXVI, 100; XXVII, 52-3
    Lawson, Ernest: XXVI, 135; XXVII, 116-7; XXIX, 35-6, 56, XXIX, 38-9, 80, 84; XXXV; XXXVIII, 64
    Lee, Charles: XXXIII, 5, 7
    Legros, Alphonse: XXXI, 10, 77
    Lever, Beatrice Sinclair: XXVI, 42, 47, 57, 86, 123-4; XXVII, 26, 33, 36, 61, 69; XXXII, 43
    Lever, Hayley: XXV, 54, 69, 83-4, 109, 119; XXVI, 37, 40, 104; XXVII, 25, 61, 78, 101, 131; XXXI, 79; XXXV, 107, 109; XXXVI, 22, 31
    Levy, John: XXIX, 56; XXX, 8, 27; XXXI, 2; XXXII, 2, 43; XXXIII, 3, 10, 23, 33; XXXV, 103; XXXVI, 61-3
    Lie, Jonas: XXVI, 44; XXVII, 116; XXIX, 52; XXXI, 79
    Lindsay, Sam; XXXVI, 36, 56-7, 72-3, 83-4
    Little, Philip: XXVII, 33, 36; XXX, 8, 39
    Londoner, Amy: XXVI, 44
    Lukeman, Augustus: XXXV, 133-4; XXXVIII, 5
    Luks, George: XXV, 89; XXVI, 42; XXVII, 48, 56, 85, 87-8, 117; XXX, 28; XXXIV, 37; XXXVI, 10; XXXVIII, 4
    Lyle, Margaret: XXV, 46
    Lyndhurst, Lord John S. Copley Jr.: XXXV, 112
    Macbeth, Robert: XXVII, 33; XXIX, 8-9; XXXII, 37; XXXIV, 15; XXXVIII, 85
    Mahon, Judge Edward: XXVII, 90
    Mallet, Mrs.: XXXV, 58
    Manning, Rose: XXXV, 92, 124; XXXVI, 22-8, 30, 65; XXXV B, 5, 8, 12-3, 18-9; XXXVIII, 54-9, 63
    Marin, John: XXIX, 39
    Martin, Homer: XXVII, 27; XXX, 45, XXXI, 67; XXXII, 4
    Mason, Henry: XXXI, 66-7; XXXVIII, 100, 199
    McBride, Henry: XXVI, 47, 96, 104; XXVII, 31, 92, 102-3; XXXI, 79; XXXIII, 11; XXXV, 25; XXXVI, 22; XXXVIII, 93
    McCameron, Robert: XXIX, 66, 71
    McCord, Mary: XXXVI, 104
    McCormack, John: XXVI, 98
    McCormick, William B.: XXXVII, 16-7
    McCullough, William: XXXV, 69; XXXVI, 49
    McDowell, Edward: XXXVIII, 82, 84
    McEvoy, Ambrose: XXIX, 63
    McManus, James G.: XXXI, 76; XXXV, 18; XXXVIII, 74, 105
    Melchers, Gary: XXVI, 44
    Meriden Property: XXIX, 53, 55; XXXIII, 23
    Merrick, Lula: XXVI, 50, 113; XXVII, 50, 69, 73, 96, 117; XXXV, 133; XXXVI, 29
    Metcalf, Willard: XXXIII, 2, 13; XXXV, 43, 81
    Milch Galleries: XXXI, 3; XXXII, 41; XXXIII
    Miller, Charles Townsend Abercrombie: XXXV, 62, 118, 122, 131, 136; XXXVI, 7, 33, 45, 58-9; XXXV B, 22; XXXVIII, 16
    Molarsky, Maurice: XXVI, 59; XXVII, 100, 112
    Moloof: XXXVI, 70
    Monstross, N. E.: XXVI, 40, 101
    Montgomery, J.: XXV, 41, 43, 107
    Morris, Dr. Charles Evans: XXXVI, 50-1
    Morse, S. F. B.: XXXVIII, 79
    Moutfort, Arnold: XXVII, 40, 51, 63, 77, 79, 88, 93, 99; XXIX, 4, 40, 44, 64
    Mowbray-Clarke: XXIX, 9
    Mozart: XXXIV, 21
    Muller, J. Frank: XXVII, 69; XXXV B, 26
    Muller, Michael: XXXVII, 29-30, 41; XXXIX, 3-4
    Muncy, Percy: XXXVI, 32; XXXVIII, 16; XXXV B, 7
    Muranyi, Gustave: XXXVII, 34
    Murphy, J. Francis: XXVI, 101-2; XXVII, 39, 42-3, 66-8, 84, 95, 100; XXIX, 56, 72-3; XXXI, 52, XXXIII, 17-8, 33; XXXV, 78; XXXVI, 24; XXXV B, 7
    Mussman, Mrs. S.: XXXVI, 47
    Myers, Jerome and Ethel: XXVII, 32-3, 79; XXX, 12; XXXVI, 20; XXXVII, 14; XXXVIII, 4, 20, 64
    Nave, Captain Royston: XXVII, 41, 51, 57-8, 64, 76, 91-7, 107-8; XXIX, 40, 70-1; XXXIV, 3-4, 13-4, 23
    Neagle, John: XXXV, 80
    Neimyer, John H.: XXIX, 44
    Nelson, George Laurence: XXVI, 51, 116; XXVII, 60, 100; XXXV, 76
    Nelson, W. H.: XXVI, 44; XXVII, 79, 99-100; XXIX, 44; XXXI, 80; XXXII, 40, 43; XXXIII, 30; XXXIV, 14-5; XXXV, 59, 77
    Newell, Glenn: XXXIII, 3, 8, 40, 43, 94
    Nielson, Isabel: XXV, 51, 88, 99; XXVI, 30
    Nielson, Raymond: XXV, 51; XXVII, 70
    Nisbet, Robert: XXVII, 101, 116; XXXI, 73; XXXVI, 23
    Nolan, Daniel: XXV, 72; XXIX, 60
    Norton, Clara: XXXIV, 13
    Nuni, Ann: XXV, 88, 91, 110, 124, 137-8; XXXVI, 7, 14, 28, 31; XXXV B, 1-5, 9, 11, 14, 17, 20, 26
    Nuni, Grove: XXXVIII, 95
    Nyerighazi, Erwin: XXXV, 128, 130; XXXVI, 7, 15-6, 20, 73; XXXV B, 8, 14
    O'Brien, Jim: XXXVIII, 34
    O'Callahan, Clinton: XXXI, 47
    O'Connor, Andrew: XXIX, 72; XXXV, 7
    O'Connor, Patricia: XXV, 107
    O'Malley, Power: XXXI, 20, 26
    O'Ryan, General John F: XXVII, 111
    Olin, Albert: XXXI, 49
    Oliver, Miss Jean N.: XXV, 37, 54-7, 70, 81, 88-90, 105; XXVI, 44, 92-3, 127; XXXI, 5; XXXV, 16
    Pach, Walter: XXVII, 112
    Palmer, Delos: XXVII, 41; XXXV, 64-5
    Palmer, Erastus: XXXII, 10; XL, 1
    Palmer, Hermann: XXXII; XXXVII, 39
    Parsons, Ruth: XXV, 111, 118-9; XXVI, 30
    Patty, W. A.: XXXIII, 9; XXXVIII, 69
    Paxton, William McGregor: XXV, 52; XXXI, 81
    Pennell, Joseph: XXIX, 63; XXX, 28; XXXI, 44; XXXVII, 15; XXXVIII
    Perkins, Parker: XXV, 56
    Pettie of Knoedlers: XXXIII, 11
    Phillips, Duncan: XXVI, 95; XXXIV, 28-9
    Pierce, Waldo: XXXVI, 79-80
    Pierpont, J.: XXXVII, 42; XXXVIII, 12, 20
    Pokras, Max: XXXVII, 35
    Pollia, Joseph: XXXVII, 35; XXXVIII; XXIX, 5
    Popp, John: XXXI, 47
    Potter, E.C.: XXXVII, 5, 17; XXXIX, 3, 7
    Potter, Louis: XXIX, 1
    Potter, Nathan D.: XXXV B; XXXVI, 5, 20, 27, 30-2, 37-8, 42-5, 69-74; 86; XXXVII, 13-7, 42; XXXVIII, 20, 91, 101; XXXIX, 3-7
    Potter, William J.: XXXVI, 68, 70, 72, 74, 79; XXXVIII, 90-1
    Poussin, Nicolo: XXXII, 3
    Powell, Widow: XXIX, 52; XXXII, 31, 41, 116; XXXV, 138
    Prendergast, Maurice: XXVII, 50, 57, 71, 89; XXXI, 53
    Prutting, J.: XXXVIII, 105
    Price, F. Newlin: XXIX, 42, 72; XXXI, 1, 77; XXXIII, 13; XXXVII, 25
    Quinn, Edmund: XXXI, 62-3; XXXVIII, 64
    Quinn, John: XXXVIII, 78
    Quistgaard, John Van Rehling: XXXVI, 106, 123-4; XXXII, 43; XXXIII, 3, 30, 33-5; XXXIV, 1, 37; XXXV, 101-3; XXXVIII, 99
    Ranger, Henry W: XXVII, 63
    Ray, Man: XXIX, 57; XXXI, 92
    Regnault, Henri: XXXIV, 21
    Rehn, Frank: XXVII, 47; XXIX, 55
    Reinhardt, Henry: XXIX, 50
    Reynolds, Sir Joshua: XXXI, 15-6
    Richter: XXVII, 89; XXIX, 18, 43
    Riley, John: XXXIII, 40-1
    Ringius, Carl: XXV, 93, 107; XXVI, 29; XXXI, 47
    Rio, Anita: XXVII, 98; XXXI, 72, 78-9; XXXV, 27; XXXVI, 11
    Ritman, Louis: XXVII, 89
    Rittenberg, Henry: XXXI, 80; XXXIII, 7; XXXVI, 74
    Robbins, John W.: XXIX, 11
    Robinson, Theodore: XXXI, 49, 76, 90-1; XXXII, 4; XXXIII, 1, 13, 15
    Robinson, Will: XXVI, 104
    Rodin, Auguste: XXV, 55
    Roosevelt, Theodore: XXXI, 64
    Rosenthal, A.: XXXI, 1
    Rosenthal, Sonia: XXIX, 46
    Rowse: XXXIII, 37
    Rungius, Carl: XXVII, 39, 101; XXXIII, 9
    Ruth, Babe: XXXV B, 30
    Ryder, A. P.: XXVII, 72; XXIX, 51; XXXVI, 1, 13; XXXV B, 2-3
    Sag Harbor, New York: XXXVIII
    Sahler, Helen: XXV, 56, 71, 99; XXVI, 92, 113; XXVII, 69
    Saint-Gaudens, Augustus: XXV, 87; XXVII, 109; XXIX, 12
    Saling, Paul: XXXVI, 36
    Sargent, J. S.: XXV, 38, 52, 72; XXVI, 85; XXIX, 60; XXX, 28; XXXI, 78; XXXIII, 10; XXXV, 34, 103; XXXVI
    Sargent, Margaret: XXX, 28
    Seymour, R. Russell: XXV, 47; XXVII, 118; XXIX, 1
    Seaton-Schmidt, Anna: XXV, 38, 91
    Shakespear: XXX, 24; XXXVIII
    Shee, Sir Martin A.: XXXIII, 43; XXXIV, 11-2
    Sherman, John: XXXI, 42
    Sherwin, Mrs. Louis: XXVI, 116; XXVII, 110; XXIX, 2
    Shurtleff, Roswell M.: XL, 1
    Sloan, John: XXV, 40, 52, 54, 68-9, 73, 85, 93-4; XXVI, 29, 64, 77-8, 99-100, 137; XXVII, 31, 35, 38-9, 112-3, 116-7; XXIX, 66; XXXI, 51; XXXII, 46
    Smith, W. H.: XXIX, 69
    Snell, Henry: XXV, 81, 100, 104; XXVII, 99; XXIX, 10
    Society of American Artists: XXXII, 11-27
    Spanish Encyclopedia: XXIX, 27
    Speicher, Eugene: XXVII, 117; XXXIII, 25; XXXVIII, 72
    Spencer, Elizabeth: XXVI, 103-4; XXXVIII, 29
    Stieglitz, Alfred: XXVI, 98; XXIX, 39
    Sterner, Marie: XXVII, 25, 79; XXXI, 27; XXXIII, 10, 12
    Sterner, Albert: XXVI, 136; XXVII, 79; XXXIII, 12; XXXVI, 20; XXXV B, 1, 3-4
    Stevenson, Gordon: XXXVI, 13-4, 21, 45, 87, 90; XXXVII, 33; XXXVIII, 6, 8, 31, 74
    Strauss, Richard: XXXVI, 41
    Stuart, Gilbert: XXVII, 19, 21; XXVII, 35; XXXIII, 43; XXXIV, 11; XXXV, 85; XXXVIII, 50
    Sully, Thomas: XXX, 15; XXXVIII, 50
    Szopory, Baron Imre: XXXV, 105, 124-7, 131, 136; XXXVI; XXXV B, 7; XXXVII, 28, 31, 39; XXXVIII, 8, 83; XXXIX, 5, 7
    Tarbell, Ed.: XXV, 96
    Thayer, Abbot: XXVII, 108
    Thompson, Juliet: XXIX, 45
    Thorp, Earl: XXXVII, 36
    Towle, Captain Ledyard: XXVII, 107
    Townsend, J. B.: XXV, 53, 64; XXVI, 42, 47, 49-50, 57-8, 84, 86, 97, 100, 104, 106, 136; XXVII, 33, 35-6, 47, 62, 80, 96; XXIX, 45, 61; XXXII, 43; XXXV, 116; XXXVIII, 4, 73
    Trotta, Guiseppe: XXVII, 91
    Tupper, Alex: XXXI, 5
    Twachtman, John: XXV, 89; XXVII, 6, 65; XXIX, 13, 16, 56-7, 61; XXX, 34, 44; XXXI, 39, 45, 48-9, 67; XXXIV, 35
    Valencampf, Theo: XXV, 51, 56, 67, 70, 91, 109, 119; XXVI, 28; XXIX, 61; XXXV, 16
    Van Cleef, Augustus: XXXVIII, 73
    Van Veen, Peter: XXXI, 67; XXXVIII, 85
    Vanderbilt, Gertrude: XXXII, 4
    Vanderlyn, John: XXXV, 87
    Vayana, Nunzio: XXVII, 118; XXXII, 34; XXXVI, 16
    Vezin, Charles: XXVII, 102; XXXVI, 65-6; XXXVII, 24
    Vincent, Harry: XXXI
    Vinton, F. P.: XXXIII, 1; XXXV
    Von Boskerk, Robert: XXVII, 85
    Von Shollay, Ruth: XXV, 51, 87-8, 96, 98; XXVI, 28; XXIX, 54, 60
    Vonnoh, Robert: XXVII, 104; XXIX, 6, 8; XXXI, 79; XXXIII, 7; XXXVI, 22; XXXV B
    Vose, Robert: XXV, 5-, 62, 118; XXVI, 33; XXVII, 46, 110; XXIX, 61; XXX, 8, 10, 42, 44; XXXI, 50; XXXVIII, 91
    Wagner, Richard: XXVI, 84
    Waitt, Marian: XXVI, 84
    Walcott, Albert: XXIX, 64; XXX, 5, 7; XXXI, 12, 15, 51, 79, 83; XXXII, 94-6; XXXV, 36
    Walker, Horatio: XXXI, 49
    Walkowitz, Abraham: XXVI, 58; XXVI, 112
    Wallace, Cornelia: XXXV, 88, 90-1, 94, 123-5, 130-7, 198; XXXVI, 7-8, 19, 26, 30, 46, 85, 87; XXXVIII, 67, 72, 74-5
    Wallace, Ruth: XXIX, 64; XXXI, 23; XXXII, 38-9; XXXIV, 3, 55, 77
    Wanda,: XXXVI, 60; XXXVII, 23
    Warner, Olin L.: XXXII, 1; XXXV, 106; XXXVIII, 64
    Washington, George: XXXV, 83
    Watrous, Harry: XXVII, 102; XXIX, 3, 21; XXXI, 83; XXXVI, 33
    Weiland, James: XXVII, 68; XXXIII, 17
    Weir, J. Alden: XXVI, 41, 136; XXVII, 43, 46; XXIX, 17; XXX, 44; XXXI, 62, 83, 87-9; XXXII, 1, 4; XXXIII, 2, 13; XXXV, 106-7, 110
    Weitenkampf, Frank: XXV, 29, 31; XXVI, 86; XXXV B, 11
    Wendell, Theodore: XXIX, 71; XXXI, 67
    West, Benjamin: XXXV, 85
    Wetherell, H. K. K.: XXXVI, 22; XXXVIII, 67
    Whistler, James: XXVII, 56; XXIX, 65
    White, Edwin: XXX, 15
    Wilson, Woodrow: XXV, 23; XXVI, 113-5; XXX, 23
    Woolf, Michael
    Woolf, Sam: XXVI, 42; XXVII, 33; XXXIII, 9; XXXV, 81; XXXVI, 14; XXXV B, 10
    Wright, Ed Ashel
    Wright, Dr. Joel: XXV, 48; XXIX, 54
    Wyant, Alexander: XXVII, 83
    Yeats, John B.: XXIX, 65, 66
    Young, Howard: XXIX, 50; XXXII, 33
    Young, Mahonri: XXVII, 34, 70; XXX, 3, 17, 20, 28; XXXI, 53; XXXV, 76, 91, 109-10; XXXV B, 14; XXXVI, 24; XXXVIII, 12; XXXVIII, 72, 92
    Zogbaum, Rufus
    Zorach, William: XXXI, 86
    - Volume XXV, 1918 June-September (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 18)
      (Apel, Marie: 52; Atwood, William E.: 50, 53, 56, 62-69, 67-70, 88, 90; Baker, Bryant: 51, 56, 62, 83, 88, 92; Bayley, Frank [Copley Gallery]: 70, 101-102; Bellows, George: 84; Bernstein, Teresa: 38, 50-55, 69, 80, 90-105; Boucher, Dr.: 3, 103-106; Brush, Franklin: 56, 63, 97, 105-7, 137; Coburn, F. W.: 62, 67, 92; Copley, John: 29, 50, 61-2, 65, 70, 73, 77-8, 86, 102-3, 108, 113-117; Downes, W. H: 28; DuBois, Guy Pene: 85, 91; Duveneck, Frank: 53, 86; Hassam, Childe: 97; Haydn, Josef; Nuni [sic], Ann: 88, 91, 110, 124, 137-8; Sargent, John Singer: 38, 52, 72; Sloan, John: 40, 52, 54, 68-9, 85, 93-4; Twachtman, John: 89; Valencampf, John: 51, 56, 67, 70, 91, 109, 119; Vose, Robert: 5-. 62, 118)
    - Volume XXVI, 1918 September-December (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 19)
      (Anderson, Oscar: 28; Apel, Marie: 44, 47, 57, 97-99; Armistice, 64-8, 76; Babcock, E. C.: 85, 90, 102-3, 112, 117, 123, 127; Bellows, George: 41-6, 187; Bernstein, Teresa: 44-6, 58-9, 63, 80-4, 90-2, 104, 133; Copley, John Singleton: 57, 81-2, 106, 109-12, 121-2, 129; Detweiller, F. 97, 119, 123-5, 130-4; Dickinson, S.E.: 48, 90, 125-7, 133; DuBois, Guy Pene: 40, 89-91; Henri, Robert: 46, 98; Higgins, Eugene: 45-6, 60, 84, 136-7; Knoedlers: 136, 180-1; Kraushaar, John: 42; Kress: 42-3; Kuehne, Max: 42; Lever, Beatrice Sinclair: 42, 47, 57, 86, 123-4; Oliver, Jean N.: 44, 9203, 127; Sloan, John: 29, 64, 77-8, 99-100, 137; Townsend, J.B.: 42, 47-50, 57-8, 84, 86, 97, 100, 104, 106, 136)
    - Volume XXVII, 1919 January-March (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 20)
      (Art Review International: 1, 59; Babcock, E.C.: 28, 41, 49, 73, 80; Bartlett, Paul: 65, 90, 109; Beal, Gifford: 28, 61, 70; Beaux, Cecilia: 54, 69, 119; Cox, Kenyon: 7, 97; Dickinson, S.E.: 40-1, 51, 56-8, 63-4, 70, 73-6, 91, 93; Expressionists: 50, 73; Granville, Smith: 38, 46, 68-9, 100-2; Griffin, Walter: 65, 71, 99-100; Henri, Robert: 53-4, 115-117; Judson, Alice: 5-6, 38-9, 41, 60, 64, 96-7; Lever, Beatrice Sinclair: 26, 33, 36, 61, 69; Luks, George: 48, 56, 85, 87-8, 117; McBride, Henry: 31, 92, 102-3; Merrick, Lula: 50, 69, 73, 96, 117; Murphy, J. Francis: 39, 42-3, 66-8, 84, 95, 100; Nave, Captain Royston: 41, 51, 57-8, 64, 76, 91-7, 107-8; Prendergast, Maurice: 50, 57, 71, 89; Weir, J. Alden: 43, 46; Young, Mahonri; 34, 70)
    - Volume XXVIII, 1919 February-July (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 21)
      (Art News, 73; Art Review International: list; Eilshemius, Louis: 89)
    - Volume XXIX, 1919 April-June (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 22)
      (Apel, Marie: 40, 70; Bayley, Frank: 4-5, 59; Daniel, Charles: 39, 42; Dickinson, S.E.: 36, 40, 64, 70-1; DuBois, Guy Pene: 72; Duveneck, Frank: 57; Flagg, Charles Noel: 41, 54; Griffin, Walter: 58; Hassam, Childe: 55; Higgins, Eugene: 3-5, 12; Kent, Rockwell: 33, 43; Knoedlers: 115; Lawson, Ernest: 35-6, 56; Macbeth, Robert: 8-9; Marin, John: 39; Price, F. Newlin: 42, 72; Ray, Man: 57; Twachtman, John: 13, 16, 56-7, 61; Yeates, John B.: 65-6)
    - Volume XXX, 1919 June-August (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 23)
      (Blakelock, R.A: 27, 42-3, 46; Borglum, Gutzon: 20; De Valera, Eamon: 1, 11; Dougherty, Paul: 3, 17; Hassam, Childe: 28; Little, Phillip: 3, 89; Young, Mahonri: 3, 17, 20, 28)
    - Volume XXXI, 1919 August-December (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 24)
      (Ainslie, George: 66, 94; Aitken, Robert J.: 38-40, 44, 46; Bellows, George: 52, 73; DuBois, Guy Pene: 62; Duveneck, Frank: 67; Flanagan, John: 38-9, 61-2; Groll, Albert: 61-2, 79; Hafner, Charles: 38, 80; Innes, George: 66; Kronberg, Louis: 3-4, 83; Milch Galleries: 3; Pennell, Joseph: 44; Prendergast, Maurice: 53; Reynolds, Sir Joshua: 15-6; Roosevelt, Theodore: 104; Twachtman, John: 39, 45, 48-9, 67; Walcott, Albert: 12, 15, 51, 79, 83; Weir, J. Alden: 62, 83, 87-9; Zorach, William: 86)
    - Volume XXXII, 1920 January-March (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 25)
      (Bartlett, Paul: 1, 34-5; Dickinson, S.E.: 5, 32-3; Dudensing: 40, 46; Flagg, Charles Noel: 41, 45; Granville, Smith W.: 4; Levy, John: 2, 43; Macbeth, Robert: 37; Palmer, Erastus: 10; Sloan, John: 46; Society of American Artists: 11-27; Vanderbilt, Gertrude: 4; Walcott, Albert: 94-6; Weir, J. Alden: 1, 4; Young, Howard: 33)
    - Volume XXXII B, 1920 (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information), (list of subscribers) (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Volume XXXIII, 1920 March-April (Box 1, Folder 27)
      (Art Review International; Beaux, Cecilia: 2; Bellows, George: 8; Bowdoin, W.G.: 2; Carroll, John: 20-4; Cortissoz, Royal: 9; Frazen, August: 33; Gay, Edward: 26, 31, 33; Groll, Albert: 8, 15; Henri, Robert: 25; Higgins, Eugene: 8, 23; Hunt, William Morris: 35, 37; Johnson, Eastman: 19; Laurens, Jean Paul: 21; McBride, Henry: 11; Murphy, J. Francis: 17-8, 33; Price, F. Newlin: 13; Rittenberg, Henry: 7; Robinson, Theodore: 1, 13, 15; Ringuis, Carl: 9; Vinton, F.P.: 1; Vonnoh, Robert: 7; Weir, J. Alden: 2, 13)
    - Volume XXXIV, 1920 May-July (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 28)
      (Barry, James: 84; Blakelock, R.A.: 37; Dickinson, S.E.: 1-4; Groll, Albert: 1-2; Hafner, Charles Andrea: 1, 14; Hoppin, Charles A.: 14, 23-4; Judson, Alice: 13; Luks, George: 37; Nave, Captain Royston: 3-4, 13-4, 23; Nelson, W.H.: 14-5; Norton, Clara: 13; Regnault, Henri: 21; Shee, Sir Martin A: 11-2; Wallace, Ruth: 3, 55, 77; )
    - Volume XXXV, 1920 July-1921 May (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 29)
      (Aitken, Robert J.: 7-8, 20, 43; Babcock, E.C.: 60, 108; Bellows, George: 43; Bunce, W. Gedney: 6, 120; Cole, Thomas Casilear 77, 120, 123, 126, 131, 136; Cross, Amy: 116; Damrosch, Helena: 134; Downey, Chris: 29; DuBois, Guy Pene: 117; Eakins, Thomas: 111; Ennis, George Pierce: 131; Foster, Ben: 107; Gay, Edward: 45, 58; Giles, Howard: 107; Goldthwait, Anne: 82; Hafner, Charles Andrew: 1, 44, 55, 57, 60, 63 ,67, 77, 90-2, 120, 129-30, 133; Hassam, Childe: 25, 80-2, 119; Higgins, Eugene: 6, 9, 20, 23, 108-109; Inman, Henry: 87; Kimbel, Richard: 123-4, 131, 169; Manning, Rose: 92, 124; Metcalf, Willard: 43, 81; Stuart, Gilbert: 85; Valenfampf, Theo: 16; Vanderlyn, John: 87; West, Benjamin: 85)
    - Volume XXXVI, 1921 September-1922 April (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 30)
      (Clivette, Merton: 48-50; Cole, Thomas Casilear: 82, 85; Cooney, John: 6, 9-10 28, 39; Detweiller, F: 6, 20-1, 37, 54-5, 77-8, 80-2, 85-7; Donner, Herman Montago: 18; Dorr, C.H.: 102; Dudensing: 88; Eakins, Thomas: 21; Fiedler, Max: 17; Frazen, August: 23; Hafner, Charles Andrew: 14, 20, 25, 73; Hassam, Childe: 10; Kitson, Henry Hudson: 66-7; Levy, John: 61-3; McBride, Henry: 22; Merrick, Lula: 29; Potter, Nathan D.: 5, 20, 27, 30-2, 27-8, 42-5, 69-74, 86; Rio, Anita: 11; A.P. Ryder: 1, 13; Vezin, Charles: 65-6; Wallace, Cornelia: 7-8, 19, 26, 30, 46, 85, 87; Young, Mahonri: 24)
    - Volume XXXVII, 1922 April-September (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 31)
      (Barile, Xavier: 29; Bellows, George: 14; Brandegee, Robert B.: 24; Crews, Floyd: 22; Daniel, Charles: 16; Escobal: 42; Haverty, J.J.: 17-21; Higgins, Eugene: 14-5; Inukai, Kyohei: 16, 39, 42; Kronberg, Louis: 23; McCormick, William B.: 16-7; Myers, Jerome and Ethel: 14; Pennell, Joseph: 15; Ranger, Henry W.: 63; Stevenson, Gordon: 33; Vezin, Charles: 24)
    - Volume XXXVIII, 1922 October-1923 June (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 32)
      (Ainslie, George: 9, 28, 33; Belcher, Hilda: 29; Burrows, Carlyle: 10, 31, 72; Chase, William M.: 3; Cheney, Russell: 18; Daniel, Charles: 3; Detweiller, F.: 14, 49, 52, 81, 88-9; Donohue, William Howard: 49; Dreier, Katherine: 89; Ennis, George Pearse: 9; Frazen, August: 36-40; Gaspard, Leon: 90-1; Granville-Smith, W.: 9; Gruppe, Charles P.: 40, 43; Hardie, Robert Gordon: 51; Hooker, J.: 105, 107; Inukai, Kyohei: 4, 8-9, 18, 20, 34-5, 40-1, 82, 88, 90-100; Judson, Alice: 9-90; Keller, Deane: 94, 103; Lawson, Ernest: 64; Luks, George: 4; Macbeth, Robert: 85; Manning, Rose: 54-9, 63; McBride, Henry: 93; McManus, James G.: 74, 105; Miller, Charles Townsend Abercrombie: 16; Morse, S.F.B.: 79; Nuni, Grove: 95; Pierpont, J.: 12, 20; Potter, Nathan D.: 20, 91, 101; Stuart, Gilbert: 50; Szopory, Baron Imre: 8, 83; Vose, Robert: 91; Young, Mahonri: 72, 92)
    - Volume XXXIX, 1923 June-December (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 33)
      (Crews, Floyd: 1; Detweiller, F.: 5; Keller, Deane: 3; Muller, Michael: 3-4; Potter, Nathan D: 3-7)
    - Volume XL, 1923 October-1924 October (See Addendum List of Names and Subjects for Content Information) (Box 1, Folder 34)
      (Copley, John Singleton: 1-2; Palmer, Erastus: 1; Shurtleff, Roswell M.: 1)